seomotionz.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy - SEO Motionz

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy

in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use

of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

When accessing our Website, SEO Motionz will learn certain information about

you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology

called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”)

and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information

gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of

visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited

just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique

identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer

for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically

designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser

if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser

only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not

the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the

Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network

to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web

server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data”

so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content

of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We

provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ

in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering

our business activities, providing customer service and making available other

items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

SEO Motionz will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you

visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will

such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties

without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words,

when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection

of our legal rights.

**A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that

minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If

you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and

guidance from your parents or guardians.

**How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason,

we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However,

doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter

on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure

Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.

SEO Motionz may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used

for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections

of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical

design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available

to all users, SEO Motionz uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify

unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

**Third Party Policy**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.

These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address,

email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order

to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like

more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this

information used by these companies.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without

notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the

future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under

this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy

Policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles

in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected

and maintained.

Contact

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our

web site, please contact us.

SEO Motionz

India

admin@seomotionz.com
